George S. Schuyler Papers
George S. Schuyler Papers
- Writings
  - Periodicals with articles by George S. Schuyler
    - Review of the News, 1971; 2 folders (Box 16)
      Volume 7 no. 44 pp. 25-26 Nov 3, 1971 (2 copies)
      Volume 7 no. 46 pp. 27-28 Nov 17, 1971
      Volume 7 no. 47 pp. 27-28 Nov 24, 1971
      Volume 7 no. 49 pp. 27-28 Dec 8, 1971
      Volume 7 no. 50 pp. 27-28 Dec 15, 1971 (2 copies)
      Volume 7 no. 51 pp. 27-28 Dec 22, 1971
      Volume 7 no. 52 pp. 27-28 Dec 29, 1971
    - Review of the News, 1972, Jan-Sep; 3 folders (Box 16)
      Volume 8 no. 1 pp. 27-28 Jan 5, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 2 pp. 25-26 Jan 12, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 3 pp. 25-26 Jan 19, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 4 pp. 27-28 Jan 26, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 5 pp. 23-24 Feb 2, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 6 pp. 25-26 Feb 9, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 7 pp. 25-26 Feb 16, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 8 pp. 25-26 Feb 23, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 9 pp. 25-26 Mar 1, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 10 pp. 25-26 Mar 8, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 11 pp. 25-26 Mar 15, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 12 pp. 25-26 Mar 22, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 13 pp. 25-26 Mar 29, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 14 pp. 27-28 Apr 5, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 15 pp. 25-26 Apr 12, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 16 pp. 25-26 Apr 19, 1972 (2 copies)
      Volume 8 no. 17 pp. 23-24 Apr 26, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 18 pp. 23-24 May 3, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 19 pp. 23-24 May 10, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 20 pp. 25-26 May 17, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 21 pp. 23-24 May 24, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 22 pp. 23-24 May 31, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 23 pp. 25-26 Jun 7, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 24 pp. 25-26 Jun 14, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 25 pp. 25-26 Jun 21, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 26 pp. 25-26 Jun 28, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 27 pp. 25-26 Jul 5, 1972 (2 copies)
      Volume 8 no. 28 pp. 25-26 Jul 12, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 29 pp. 25-26 Jul 19, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 30 pp. 25-26 Jul 26, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 31 pp. 25-26 Aug 2, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 32 pp. 25-26 Aug 9, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 33 pp. 25-26 Aug 16, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 34 pp. 25-26 Aug 23, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 35 pp. 25-26 Aug 30, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 36 pp. 25-26 Sep 6, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 37 pp. 25-26 Sep 13, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 38 pp. 25-26 Sep 20, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 39 pp. 25-26 Sep 27, 1972
    - Review of the News, 1972, Oct-Dec (Box 17)
      Volume 8 no. 40 pp. 25-26 Oct 4, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 41 pp. 25-26 Oct 11, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 42 pp. 25-26 Oct 18, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 44 pp. 23-24 Nov 1, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 45 pp. 25-26 Nov 8, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 46 pp. 25-26 Nov 15, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 47 pp. 25-26 Nov 22, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 48 pp. 25-26 Nov 29, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 50 [numbered incorrectly by publisher] pp. 25-26 Dec 6, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 50 pp. 25-26 Dec 13, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 51 pp. 25-26 Dec 20, 1972
      Volume 8 no. 52 pp. 25-26 Dec 27, 1972
    - Review of the News, 1973; 4 folders (Box 17)
      Volume 9 no. 1 pp. 25-26 Jan 3, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 2 pp. 25-26 Jan 10, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 3 pp. 25-26 Jan 17, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 4 pp. 25-26 Jan 24, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 5 flyer Jan 31, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 5 pp. 25-26 Jan 31, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 6 pp. 25-26 Feb 7, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 7 pp. 25-26 Feb 14, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 8 pp. 25-26 Feb 21, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 9 pp. 25-26 Feb 28, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 10 pp. 25-26 Mar 7, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 11 pp. 25-26 Mar 14, 1973 (2 copies)
      Volume 9 no. 12 pp. 25-26 Mar 21, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 13 pp. 25-26 Mar 28, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 14 pp. 25-26 Apr 4, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 15 pp. 25-26 Apr 11, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 16 pp. 25-26 Apr 18, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 17 pp. 25-26 Apr 25, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 18 pp. 25-26 May 2, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 19 pp. 25-26 May 9, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 20 pp. 25-26 May 16, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 21 pp. 25-26 May 23, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 22 pp. 25-26 May 30, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 23 pp. 25-26 Jun 6, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 24 pp. 25-26 Jun 13, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 25 pp. 25-26 Jun 20, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 26 pp. 25-26 Jun 27, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 28 pp. 25-26 Jul 11, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 29 pp. 25-26 Jul 18, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 30 pp. 25-26 Jul 25, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 31 pp. 25-26 Aug 1, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 32 pp. 25-26 Aug 8, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 33 pp. 25-26 Aug 15, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 34 pp. 25-26 Aug 22, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 35 pp. 25-26 Aug 29, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 36 pp. 25-26 Sep 5, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 37 pp. 25-26 Sep 12, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 38 pp. 25-26 Sep 19, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 39 pp. 25-26 Sep 26, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 40 pp. 23-24 Oct 3, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 41 pp. 25-26 Oct 10, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 42 pp. 23-24 Oct 17, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 43 pp. 23-24 Oct 24, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 44 pp. 23-24 Oct 31, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 45 pp. 23-24 Nov 7, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 46 pp. 23-24 Nov 14, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 47 pp. 23-24 Nov 21, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 48 pp. 23-24 Nov 28, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 49 pp. 25-26 Dec 5, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 50 pp. 25-26 Dec 12, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 51 pp. 23-24 Dec 19, 1973
      Volume 9 no. 52 pp. 23-24 Dec 26, 1973 (2 copies)
    - Review of the News, 1974, Jan-Mar (Box 17)
      Volume 10 no. 1 pp. 23-24 Jan 2, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 2 pp. 23-24 Jan 9, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 3 pp. 23-24 Jan 16, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 4 pp. 25-26 Jan 23, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 5 pp. 23-24 Jan 30, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 6 pp. 23-24 Feb 6, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 7 pp. 23-24 Feb 13, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 8 pp. 23-24 Feb 20, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 9 pp. 23-24 Feb 27, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 11 pp. 23-24 Mar 13, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 12 pp. 25-26 Mar 20, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 13 pp. 23-24 Mar 27, 1974
    - Review of the News, 1974, Apr-Dec; 3 folders (Box 18)
      Volume 10 no. 15 pp. 25-26 Apr 10, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 16 pp. 23-24 Apr 17, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 17 pp. 25-26 Apr 24, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 18 pp. 23-24 May 1, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 19 pp. 21-22 May 8, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 20 pp. 21-22 May 15, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 21 pp. 23-24 May 22, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 22 pp. 25-26 May 29, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 23 pp. 23-24 Jun 5, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 24 pp. 23-24 Jun 12, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 25 pp. 23-24 Jun 19, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 26 pp. 23-24 Jun 26, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 27 pp. 23-24 Jul 3, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 28 pp. 23-24 Jul 10, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 29 pp. 23-24 Jul 17, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 30 pp. 23-24 Jul 24, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 31 pp. 23-24 Jul 31, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 32 pp. 25-26 Aug 7, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 33 pp. 23-24 Aug 14, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 34 pp. 23-24 Aug 21, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 35 pp. 25-26 Aug 28, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 36 pp. 23-24 Sep 4, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 37 pp. 25-26 Sep 11, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 38 pp. 23-24 Sep 18, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 39 pp. 23-24 Sep 25, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 41 pp. 23-24 Oct 9, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 42 pp. 23-24 Oct 16, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 43 pp. 23-24 Oct 23, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 44 pp. 23-24 Oct 30, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 45 pp. 25-26 Nov 6, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 46 pp. 25-26 Nov 13, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 47 pp. 23-24 Nov 20, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 48 pp. 25-26 Nov 27, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 49 pp. 25-26 Dec 4, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 50 pp. 23-24 Dec 11, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 51 pp. 25-26 Dec 18, 1974
      Volume 10 no. 52 pp. 23-24 Dec 25, 1974
    - Review of the News, 1975, Jan-Sep; 3 folders (Box 18)
      Volume 11 no. 1 pp. 23-24 Jan 1, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 2 pp. 23-24 Jan 8, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 3 pp. 23-24 Jan 15, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 4 pp. 25-26 Jan 22, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 5 pp. 23-24 Jan 29, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 6 pp. 21-22 Feb 5, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 7 pp. 23-24 Feb 12, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 8 pp. 23-24 Feb 19, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 9 pp. 23-24 Feb 26, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 10 pp. 21-22 Mar 5, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 11 pp. 23-24 Mar 12, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 13 pp. 23-24 Mar 26, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 14 pp. 23-24 Apr 2, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 15 pp. 23-24 Apr 9, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 16 pp. 23-24 Apr 16, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 17 pp. 23-24 Apr 23, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 18 pp. 23-24 Apr 30, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 19 pp. 23-24 May 7, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 20 pp. 23-24 May 14, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 21 pp. 23-24 May 21, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 22 pp. 23-24 May 28, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 23 pp. 23-24 Jun 4, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 24 pp. 23-24 Jun 11, 1974
      Volume 11 no. 25 pp. 23-24 Jun 18, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 26 pp. 23-24 Jun 25, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 27 pp. 23-24 Jul 2, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 28 pp. 23-24 Jul 9, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 29 pp. 23-24 Jul 16, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 30 pp. 23-24 Jul 23, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 31 pp. 23-24 Jul 30, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 32 pp. 23-24 Aug 6, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 33 pp. 23-24 Aug 13, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 34 pp. 25-26 Aug 20, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 35 pp. 25-26 Aug 27, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 36 pp. 25-26 Sep 3, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 37 pp. 23-24, The Films Sep 10, 1975 (Beginning here and subsequent issues Schuyler's column was called "The Films"
      Volume 11 no. 38 pp. 23-24 Sep 17, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 39 pp. 23-24 Sep 24, 1975
    - Review of the News, 1975, Oct-Dec (Box 19)
      Volume 11 no. 40 pp. 23-24 Oct 1, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 41 pp. 23-24 Oct 8, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 42 pp. 23-24 Oct 15, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 43 pp. 23-24 Oct 22, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 44 pp. 25-26 Oct 29, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 45 pp. 23-24 Nov 5, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 46 pp. 25-26 Nov 12, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 47 pp. 25-26 Nov 19, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 48 pp. 23-24 Nov 26, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 49 pp. 25-26 Dec 3, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 50 pp. 23-24 Dec 10, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 52 pp. 23-24 Dec 24, 1975
      Volume 11 no. 53 pp. 21-22 Dec 31, 1975
    - Review of the News, 1976, Jan-Jul; 2 folders (Box 19)
      Volume 12 no. 1 pp. 25-26 Jan 7, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 2 pp. 23-24 Jan 14, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 3 pp. 25-26 Jan 21, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 4 pp. 23-24 Jan 28, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 5 pp. 25-26 Feb 4, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 6 pp. 23-24 Feb 11, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 7 pp. 23-24 Feb 18, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 8 pp. 23-24 Feb 25, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 9 pp. 23-24 Mar 3, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 10 pp. 25-26 Mar 10, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 11 pp. 25-26 Mar 17, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 12 pp. 35-36 Mar 24, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 13 pp. 25-26 Mar 31, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 14 pp. 25-26 Apr 7, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 16 pp. 25-26 Apr 21, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 17 pp. 23-24 Apr 28, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 18 pp. 25-26 May 5, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 19 pp. 21-22, The Films May 12, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 21 pp. 21-22 May 26, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 22 pp. 21-22 Jun 2, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 23 pp. 21-22 Jun 9, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 24 pp. 21-22 Jun 16, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 25 pp. 21-22 Jun 23, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 26 pp. 21-22 Jun 30, 1976 [MISSING Dec 2018]
      Volume 12 no. 27 pp. 21-22 Jul 7, 1976
      Volume 12 no. 28 pp. 21-22 Jul 14, 1976
    - Review of the News, 1967 (Box 19)
      v.16 no.12 Apr 28, 1967 "Dialogue With a John Bircher" - interview with George Schuyler
    - St. John Fisher Pioneer (Oversize 7)
    - Sepia, 1962 (Oversize 7)
      Vol. 11 no. 5 pp. 55-58, "Freedom Through Finance" May 1962
    - The Sepia Socialite, 1942 (Oversize 7)
      Apr 1942 pp. 3, 5, 16, 82, "Forward: A Look at Negro Louisiana"
  - Periodicals with articles by George S. Schuyler
    - [bound volume, contains several issues of various periodicals], 1932-1947 (Box 19)
      The American Parade, vol. III no. 1 (Oct/Nov/Dec 1928) 54-61, "Racial Intermarriage in the United States"
      Opportunity: Journal of Negro Life, vol. XV no. 12 (Dec 1937) 377-378 (review) American Stuff by Henry G. Alsberg; vol. X no. 12 (Dec 1932) 388-389 (review) Georgia Nigger by John L. Spivak; vol. X no. 8 (Aug 1932) 257-258 (review) Race, Class, and Party by Paul Lewinson
      Harlem: A Forum of Negro Life, vol. 1 no. 1 (Nov 1928) 17-20, "Woof"
      Opportunity: Journal of Negro Life, vol. X no. 6 (Jun 1932) 175-176, "Mr. Embree Discovers a New Race"
      Birth Control Review: A Negro Number, vol. XVI no. 6 (Jun 1932) 165-166, "Quality vs. Quantity"
      The Forum: A Quarterly Review, vol. 2 no. 1 (Dec 1932) 18-20, "The Economic Outlook for the Negro" vol. 2 no. 4 (Sep 1933) 27-28, "The Negro of American Literature"
      The Kaleidoscope, vol. 1 no. 4 (Apr 14, 1934) 13, "When Black Weds White"
      The Record of Girl's Friendly Society of the U.S.A., vol. XLV no. 1 (Jan 1937) 244, 252, "Where Schools Count Most"
      Cultural Freedom, (Jun 1940) 1-3, "Cultural Freedom and the American Negro"
      Politics, vol. 1 no. 6 (Jul 1944) 181-182 (review) An American Dilemma: The Negro Problem and Modern Democracy by Gunnar Myrdal vol. 2 no. 5 (May 1945) 137, "F. D. R."
      Interracial Review: A Journal for Christian Democracy, vol. XIX no. 4 (Apr 1946) 54-55, "The Negro and Communism"
      The Negro Book Club News, vol. 1 no. 2 (Oct 194[?]) 3, "What's Wrong With Negro Writers"
      The Negro South, vol. X no. 1 (Dec 1946) 16-18, "The Future of the Northern Negro in Politics"
      Circuit, vol. 2 no. 8 (Jan 1947) 4-5, "A Date With Destiny for Women in 1947".
    - [bound volume, contains issues of various periodicals], 1950-1956 (Box 20)
      The Freeman, vol. 1 no. 6 (Dec 11, 1950) 176-177, "The Pro-Slavery Propagandists"; vol. 2 no. 3 (Nov 5, 1951) 93-94, review of The Negro and the Communist Party, by Wilson Record; vol. 2 no. 4 (Nov 19, 1951) 117-118, "New Masks for Old" (vol. 1 printing error); vol. 2 no. 21 (Jul 14, 1952) 697-700, "FEPC is a Fraud"; vol. 3 no. 8 (Jun 1, 1953) 643-644 (review) "Clash of Cultures" Blanket Boy, by Peter Lanham and A. S. Mopeli-Paulus; vol. 4 no. 16 (May 3, 1954) 560, "Will the South Secede?"; vol. 4 no. 13 (Mar 22, 1954) 461-462, reviews of The Negro in American Life and Thought: The Nadir, 1877-1901, by Rayford W. Logan and Breakthrough on the Color Front by Lee Nichols
      National Review, vol. 1 no. 4 (Dec 14, 1955) 28-29 (review) "More Rivers to Cross" How Far the Promised Land? by Wallace
      The Freeman, vol. 6 no. 3 (Mar, 1956) 14-16, "The Case for the Private School"
    - [bound volume, includes issues of several periodicals], 1929-1937 (Box 20)
      La Releve, vol. no. 7 (Jan 1937) photo, 2-6, "Quelques Considerations de Mr. Schuyler: Haiti et l'Amerique Noire" [in French]
      The Modern Quarterly, vol. V no. 3 (Fall 1929) 361-363, "Emancipated Women and the Negro"; vol. V no. 4 (Winter 1930/1931) viii, 561-563, (review by John Chamberlin) Not Without Laughter by Langston Hughes and Black Manhattan by James Weldon Johnson and pp. 571-572 (review) Black Genesis by Samuel G. Stoney and Gertrude M. Shelby.
    - [bound volume, includes issues of several periodicals], 1931-1950 (Box 20)
      The Modern Monthly, vol. VIII no. 1 (Feb 1934) 11-17, "When Black Weds White"
      The Modern Quarterly, vol. XI no. 7 (Fall 1940) 84-87, "The Negro in the New Order"
      The Spirit of Missions, vol. XCVI no. 2 (Feb 1931) 87-90, "Negro Critic Appraisis Institute Schools"
      The Wheatsheaf, no. 419 (May 1931) 73-74, "Some Impressions of England"
      Cooperation, vol. VXII no. 8 (Aug 1931) 144-145, "The American Negro's Salvation
      Transatlantic, vol. 1 no. 6 (Feb 1944) 13-15, "Harlem: Half-way to Heaven"
      Phylon: The Atlanta University Review of Race and Culture, vol. XI no. 4 (1950) 362-368, "Phylon Profile; XXII: Carl Van Vechten"
    - Miscellaneous, 1928; 1947,; 1965,; 1968,; 1969,; undated (Box 20)
  - Periodicals, with articles about George S. Schuyler or Philippa Schuyler
    - The American Writer, Vol. 1, Nov 1, 1946 (Box 20)
    - Arlington House publishers catalogue, 1968/1969 (Box 20)
    - The Banner, p. 24, (review) Vander Ploeg, John. "New Books" Black and Conservative, Jul 7, 1967 (Box 20)
    - Carver Federal Savings, on Philippa Schuyler in the Negro History Calendar, Jan 1972; 2 copies (Box 21)
    - CLA Journal, v. XVIII no. 2 pp. 242-257, reprint, Peplow, Michael W. "George Schuyler, Satirist: Rhetorical Devices in Black No More", Dec 1974 (Box 21)
    - The Crisis, 1937; 1967,; 1976 (Box 21)
      Vol. 44 no. 6 pp. 165, 167, "Next Month"; pp. 184-185, "NAACP Youth Council News"; and pp. 188-189, "Letters from Readers" Jun 1937
      Vol. 74 no. 2 pp. 68-71, Weinberger, Andrew. "Interracial Marriage in the U.S.A."; pp. 72-78, 101, Springarn, Arthur B. "Books: By Negro Authors in 1966" Mar 1967
      Vol. 74 no. 5 pp. 248, 258, "Editorial:... and Philippa Duke Schuyler", obituary Jun 1967
      Vol. 83 no. 1 pp. 7-10, Peplow, Michael. "The Black 'Picaro' in Schuyler's Black No More" Jan 1976
    - Demography, 1970; 1973 (Box 21)
      Vol. 7 no. 3 pp. 287-299, reprint, Monahan, Thomas P. "Interracial Marriage: Data for Philadelphia and Pennyslvania" Aug 1970
      Vol. 7 no. 45 pp. 23-24, Nov 7, 1973 [MISSING Dec 2018]
    - The Economic Facts of Life, Vol. 21 no. 7, Clark, Fred G. and Richard S. Rimanoczy. "The Realistic Black Man's Burden", Jul 1968 (Box 21)
    - Esquire, pp. 76-77, Lewis, Sinclair. "Books: 'Gentlemen, This is Revolution'", Jun 1945; 2 copies (Box 21)
    - The Freeman, Vol. 16 no. 12 pp. 53-56, Chamberlin, John. "Black and Conservative", Dec 1966 (Box 21)
    - Life, "The Real American Negro", May 7, 1959; clipping (Box 21)
    - The Midwest Journal, Vol. V no. 2 pp. 24-45, Winslow, Henry F. "George S. Schuyler: Fainting Traveller", Summer 1953 (Box 21)
    - Modern Age, Vol. 11 no. 1 pp. 96-98, Lyons, Eugene. "Reviews: One Who Overcame," on Black and Conservative, Winter 1966-1967 (Box 21)
    - National Program Letter, "A Negro Speaks", Jan 1967; 2 copies (Box 21)
    - National Review, Vol. XXIII no. 35 pp. 978-989, Simonds, C. H. "The Strange Story of Willis Carto", Sep 10, 1971 (Box 21)
    - The New Yorker, 1972 (Box 21)
      Vol. XLVIII no. 41 pp. 60-120, Anderson, Jervis. "Profiles: A. Philip Randolph - 1" Dec 2, 1972
      Vol. XLVIII no. 42 pp. 48-106, Anderson, Jervis. "Profiles: A. Philip Randolph - 2" Dec 9, 1972
      Vol. XLVIII no. 43 pp. 40-85, Anderson, Jervis. "Profiles: A. Philip Randolph - 3" Dec 16, 1972
    - The Oral History Collection of Columbia University Catalogue pp. 107-108, "Biographical Section", 1964 (Box 21)
      See also Writings: Transcripts, interviews: Interview by William T. Ingersoll for copy of transcript, 725 pages.
    - Our World, Vol. 7 no. 8 pp. 46-53, "Haiti Goes to the Movies", Aug 1952 (Oversize 7)
    - Pageant, Vol. 10 no. 5 pp. 22-27, "Who Are the Six Real Top Anti-Communists?", Nov 1954; 2 copies (Box 21)
    - The PTA Magazine, Vol. 62 no. 4 pp. 12-14, Ferguson, Charles W. "Americans Not Everyone Knows: Philippa Duke Schuyler", Dec 1967 (Box 21)
    - Social Forces, Vol. 48 no. 4 pp. 461-473, reprint, Monahan, Thomas P. "Are Interracial Marriages Really Less Stable?", Jun 1970 (Box 21)
    - A Spectrum of Conservative Views, Baltimore County Public Library, bibliography (Box 21)
  - Periodicals, miscellaneous
    - Survey Graphic, Vol. XXXI no. 11 [MISSING Dec 2018], Nov 1942
  - Transcripts, interviews
    - Interview by William T. Ingersoll, Oral History Collection of Columbia University, pp. 1-200, 1960; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Interview by William T. Ingersoll, Oral History Collection of Columbia University, pp. 201-725, 1960; 5 folders (Box 22)
    - Interview by Carl Bode, regarding association with H. L. Mencken., Oct 30, 1964 (Box 22)
  - Typescripts, periodical
    - American Mercury, 1967 (Box 22)
      H. L. Mencken Nov 28, 1967
    - American Opinion, 1965-1967 (Box 22)
      Sep 15, 1965 Let Negroes Give Thanks
      Jun 16, 1966 Booker T. Washington and Sidney J. Phillips
      Dec 26, 1966 Requiem for the "Revolution"
      Feb 22, 1967 Our Avant-Garde Clergy
      Jun 29, 1967 June Moon in Africa
      Aug 4, 1967 Africa
      Aug 6, 1967 Style: The Great Journalistic Casualty
      Sep 3, 1967 From Africa
      Sep 5, 1967 Requiem for Babbit
      Oct 3, 1967 Why Our Cities Ro
      Oct 5, 1967 From Africa
      Oct 27, 1967 Review: Not Yet Uhuru
      Oct 30, 1967 Hellfare (missing and was not filmed)
      Oct 30, 1967 From Africa
      Nov 4, 1967 From Africa
      Nov 29, 1967 The Mini-Crusaders
      Dec 2, 1967 From Africa
      Dec 3, 1967 Review: The Crisis of the Negro Intellectual
      Dec 26, 1967 The Reds and I
    - American Opinion, 1968 (Box 22)
      Jan 1, 1968 From Africa
      Jan 31, 1968 From Africa
      Feb 29, 1968 From Africa
      Mar 4, 1968 Homo on the Range, revised
      Apr 7, 1968 From Africa
      May 1, 1968 The Middle East
      May 4, 1968 Moishe Tshombe
      Jul 12, 1968 From Africa
      Aug 6, 1968 From Africa
      Aug 24, 1968 The Degradation of Democracy
      Sep 6, 1968 From Africa
      Oct 1, 1968 From Africa
      Nov 3, 1968 From Africa
      Dec 2, 1968 Realists of the Battle for Biafra
    - American Opinion, 1969 (Box 22)
      Jan 1, 1969 The Carefree Mini-States
      Jan 5, 1969 The Semantic Jungle
      Jan 13, 1969 Another Bright Star in the Sky
      Jan 31, 1969 Portugal Laughs Last
      Feb 3, 1969 Review: The American Fighting Man
      Mar 4, 1969 Africa's Vanishing Fictions
      Apr 3, 1969 Grief in Lilliput
      Apr 14, 1969 Review: On Communism
      Apr 16, 1969 Review: Three-fifths of a Man
      Apr 25, 1969 Review: The Portugal Story
      May 2, 1969 Africa
      Jun 30, 1969 Shades of 'Chinese' Gordon!
      Aug 4, 1969 Filling the Red Sea Vacuum
      Sep 14, 1969 Birth of a Nation
      Dec 9, 1969 Imaginary Emigrants
    - American Opinion, 1970-1971 (Box 22)
      Jan 7, 1970 Ralph is Tired!
      Feb 7, 1970 Patton: Tribute to the C. F. R.
      Feb 11, 1970 Requiem for Utopia
      Mar 13, 1970 Daniel in the Panther's Den
      May 5, 1970 The Red Network of Africa
      Sep 2, 1970 Down the Drain
      Dec 6, 1970 Liberalism Passes On
      Mar 26, 1971 Write Off the Middle East!
      Jun 29, 1971 Red Camp on Camera
      undated The New Look in Southern Africa,
    - Modern Age, 1967-1968 (Box 23)
      Review: Centuries of Frustration: The Secret City and NAACP: A History of the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1967
      Review: The Black Power Syndrome: Black Power and Urban Unrest by Nathan Wright Jr. and Black Power by Stokley Carmichael, Jan 30, 1968
    - North American Newspaper Alliance (NANA), 1965-1968 (Box 23)
      Aug 18, 1965 Anatomy of Black Insurrection
      Aug 29, 1965 Negro Has Two Revolutions - Real and Phony
      Sep 23, 1965 Civil Rights Tripped by Labor Rights
      Oct 31, 1965 Negroes Who Don't Need to be "Saved"
      Dec 8, 1965 An Upcoming Happy New Year for Negroes
      May 8, 1966 Rights Leaders Reviving the Revolution
      Jun 8, 1966 Mississippi True to Form
      Jul 24, 1966 Negro Rioting No Surprise to Informed
      Sep 17, 1966 Sharing the Blame for Civil Rights
      Dec 3, 1966 Powell: "To Be or Not to Be"
      Dec 18, 1966 The Great Republican Dilemma
      Jan 10, 1967 The Rising Tide of Black Racism
      Mar 26, 1967 Our Canebreak Cassandra Threatens More Grief
      Jun 24, 1967 Negro Leaders in Dilemma
      Jul 26, 1967 Insurrection: The Failure of Negro Leadership
      Aug 8, 1967 The "Revolution's" Upcoming Whitewash
      Sep 10, 1967 Negro Leaders Not Remorseful
      Dec 6, 1967 Dr. King Invokes Yuletide Spirit
      1967 NAACP Hits the Sawdust Trail
      Jan 12, 1968 Subsidies for Civil Turmoil